footballscoop.com 2010-12-30

# Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting the Coaching News Network, LLC, Footballscoop.com web site. This Privacy Policy contains information about the Coaching News Network, LLC, commitment to your privacy, including: 

The information we collect and how we use it; 

Your rights to access or update your personally identifiable information; 

Your right to opt-out of receiving communications from us; and 

Our pledge to have reasonable security measured in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control. 

**Note:** This Privacy Policy only applies to this footballscoop.com web site, and not to Coaching News Network's offline practices. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the web sites of other companies, individuals or organizations to which we may provide links. These web sites may have different policies relating to your privacy and information they collect about you. Visitors should consult other sites' privacy policies, as Coaching News Network, LLC, has no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, third parties. 

**INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE**

The footballscoop.com web site collects two kinds of information from you: (1) personal information that you submit to us, and (2) non-personal information, such as the pages you visited on our site and your IP address. To learn how to opt-out of receiving further information from Coaching News Network, LLC, see the section marked "CHOICE" below. 

**Personal Information:**

We collect and use personally identifiable information about you in the following ways: 

**When You Sign Up To Receive Our Newsletters**

You may supply Coaching News Network, LLC, with your personal information when you sign up to receive our newsletters. This information may include account contact information, your name, address, telephone and fax number, email address and web address. By supplying us with this information, you consent to our sending you information such as newsletters, product information, and advertisements that we believe may interest you. If you do not wish to receive such information, see the CHOICE section, below. Coaching News Network, LLC, may, from time to time, change the information that it requests from the visitors to its web site. 

**E-mail**

If you submit feedback, questions or requests for information about the Coaching News Network, LLC, products and services, we may request your name, mailing address, telephone number and e-mail address in order to respond to your inquiries. Coaching News Network, LLC, may collect and store the information you choose to provide us to send you information about Coaching News Network, LLC, from time to time. 

**Surveys and Promotions**

From time to time, we may request information from you via surveys or online promotions such as contests and sweepstakes. Participation is completely voluntary; you have a choice whether or not to disclose any information. Information requested may include personal contact information such as your name, shipping address, phone number or e-mail address. This information may be used to contact users with further information about Coaching News Network, LLC, products and services, to notify winners and award prizes, and to monitor or improve use and satisfaction of this site. 

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

We collect and use non-personally identifiable information about you in the following ways: 

Cookies: A cookie is a piece of data placed on your hard drive when you visit our site. Cookies help us track traffic to our site, helping us identify what parts of our site interest visitors most. We do not link cookie information with any personally identifiable information. 

Referrers, IP Addresses and Environmental Variables the Coaching News Network, LLC, may also collect information through "referrers," IP addresses and various environmental variables. A "referrer" is information the web browser passes along to the Coaching News Network, LLC, web server that references the URL from which you came. An "IP Address" is a number used by computers on a network to identify your computer so that data can be transmitted to you. An "environmental variable" may include, among other things, the domain from which you access the Internet, the time you accessed our site, the type of web browser and operating system or platform used, the Internet address or the website you left to visit the footballscoop.com site, the pages you visit while at our site and the Internet address of the website you then visit. Coaching News Network, LLC, may collect IP Address information in order to administer our web site and to gather broad demographic information. 

**Information Sharing:** We share your personal information with third parties or other parties whose products or services we believe may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to share your information in this manner, please see the "CHOICE" section below. Coaching News Network, LLC,  also reserves the right to disclose your personal and non-personal information if Coaching News Network, LLC, reasonably believes it is required to do so by law; to protect itself or to protect the rights of another user; to reduce risk of credit or other kind of fraud; or to comply with a court order. 

Coaching News Network, LLC, may also share your personally and non-personally identifiable information with third parties that help manage our web site, newsletters, databases, order fulfillment and shipping, and with our third party affiliates, partners and sponsors. Coaching News Network, LLC, newsletter providers may have separate privacy policies, which we encourage our users to read. 

Finally, in the unlikely event that all or substantially all of our assets relating to this web site is sold or transferred to another party, your personal and non-personally identifiable information may be transferred to this acquiring entity. 

**Third Party Links:** This web site may contain links to other sites. Additionally, third parties may from time to time link to the Fresh Market web site. PLEASE BE AWARE THAT WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE CONTENT OR PRACTICES OF ANY OTHER SITES. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that they visit. This privacy statement applies solely to this footballscoop.com web site. 

CHOICE 

Coaching News Network, LLC, provides you with the following choices regarding the use of your information: 

You may set your browser to: (1) inform you when cookies are being set before a cookie are stored; (2) not accept cookies at all; and (3) erase all cookies from your hard drive. However, if you choose to reject or erase cookies, your ability to navigate this site may be limited. 

You may choose to not provide us with any contact information. However, if you do so, we will be unable to process your orders, respond to your inquiries, or enter you into any promotions. Furthermore, your ability to navigate this site may be impaired. 

If you do not want to us to share your information with third parties or send you further information about our products, please send an e-mail to mail@footballscoop.com 

If you would like to opt-out of receiving further information from us and would like us to remove your name from our on-line mailing list, please send an e-mail to [mail@footballscoop.com](mailto:mail@footballscoop.com).  Please include your name and e-mail address in the body of the e-mail and reference "Remove me from mailing list" on the subject line. 

If you would like to change or modify information you have previously provided us, please send an e-mail to mail@footballscoop.com 

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or the practices of our web site, please contact us at mail@footballscoop.com 

**NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our privacy policy so you will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify you by way of email. You will then have a choice as to whether or not we may use your information in this manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

**SECURITY**

We make every effort to have reasonable security procedures in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control.  If you have any questions about the security of our web site, please contact [mail@footballscoop.com](mailto:mail@footballscoop.com)

 **INSOLVENCY**

In the unlikely event that Coaching News Network, LLC, ever becomes insolvent and seeks protection under the Bankruptcy laws, Coaching News Network, LLC, may share your personal information and non-personal information with a third party that intends to continue business subject to this privacy policy, as it may be amended from time to time. 

Effective Date: June 2, 2008
